unique features of IC lom's new health
insurance product uh thank you first of
all and I think uh there are many unique
features in this product uh uh first of
all this is a completely modular in
nature the product which we have
designed the name of the product is El
uh the key add-ons the features which we
have introduced in this product one is
uh infinite care cover which is given to
the customers in this cover we are
introducing ing industry first feature
which is in the lifetime of the policy
customer can request and Avail claim of
any unlimited amount but it can be
claimed only once throughout the
lifetime of the policy this cover today
is not available in the industry itself
so this is a very unique cover which is
there and for the very first time IC is
really proud to have introduced for the
larger audience of the market so how
does the inter sub insurance
F uh see today largely whatever products
are available in the market uh maximum
uh have a capping they tell you that
today the some insured can be 5 lakh or
10 lakh or 20 lakh or 30 lakh or 50 lakh
something of that sort uh typically any
any good customer would always want to
have a security a peace of mind that
what if my claim amount or if if I want
to uh get a higher some insured to to to
solve that Pro problem what we have done
is we have introduced unlimited some
insured option in our new product
Elevate here customer can has a option
to choose from 5 lakh some insurance to
up till unlimited times cust some
insurance whatever he wants to choose
from so this is for the very first time
uh and it's a interesting leading uh
feature which we have introduced in our
product so what makes the B booster and
on signic addition
to uh again as you know we are a we are
we are a big population in our country
uh we are number one population wise our
country right now has one out of three
people are suffering from diabetes and
it is growing day by day uh as that
population is growing and then there are
so many uh ailments which are coming
there are so many uh things which are
people are suffering from all those
customers today typically in any health
insurance plans has to wait for a
certain time to get those ailments
covered in their normal policy by virtue
of elevate by virtue of jump start
add-on which we have given in our
product this waiting period is now
getting reduced to 31 days so that is
the unique feature which is again there
in our product
Elevate so what type of coverage does
elevate provide so it provide a very
comprehensive coverage it is completely
modular it is very much
personalized uh it has so many options
for any customer to obtain he can select
whatever he wants from a variety of
add-on functions which are most most of
them are best in class uh new to the
industry or or best in the industry so
it is given a complete a complete peace
of mind and more importantly a wide
range of options to choose from
sir what is the advantage of infinite
Assurance add on for individuals with
preexisting conditions so as I said this
is this is one uh jump start feature
which is there which we call jump start
it gives the flexibility of to customer
to start to get their PDS cover from
very 31st day so that is a feature that
is a thing which which is getting
covered from 31st day all PDS will get
covered in this plan why is the launch
of elate considered Health urinary step
in the health insurance according to I
number so many I think I request you
know why is the launch of el considered
a step in the health insurance industry
according to I so the Elevate product is
an industry first as VI also mentioned
none of the companies have been offering
such an unlimited cover to any uh you
know policy holder so that is why iard
feels that it is a very unique
positioning of the you know in the
health insurance industry it's a
revolutionary product for the health
insurance industry and it will benefit
the
customer so how does el C need for
personalized health
insurance so the base plan which is
there a customer can choose a base plan
and on top of that he can add any
options which he wants rather than
taking a customized rather than taking a
standard on product which is available
in the market here he can customize
according to his needs or his future
requirements that is why it's a
different product completely
thank you thank you
sir how does the integration in
enh
experience yes I think we are really
very excited because this is the first
product in the market which is bagged or
enabled by AI what we have done since
this product gives power to to customer
to choose from variety of options which
are available uh at times we think that
mean uh there has to be some
recommendation which should go from our
side to the customer what he should
buy so what we have done is we have
basis the personas of customer we have
we have uh integrated our systems there
algorithms which are made and hence in
our systems for any customer we are
recommending a plan with some add-ons
which he should be buying basis our
recommendation tool basis his demography
basis his uh other personas which are we
are capturing at the time of sale so in
a way we are trying to help customer out
to tell him that hey look these are the
add-ons you should buy but this is just
a recommendation still customer has full
choice to add or delete whatever he
wants last question is like what makes
the power Boer add sign add to the it is
very unique feature in the market
because power booster is one feature
which gives a bonus of 100% year on year
typically in our Market uh the bonus
which is given is to the tune of 2x 4X
5x or at in sometimes up till 10x
there's a limitation to that in our
product we have said irrespective of
claim your bonus will keep on increasing
year on year up to unlimited time so it
will keep on growing until you keep on
renewing the policy so as simple as that
and again this is industry first feature
which we have launched in
our thank you thank you very much a
[Music]